Assignment: Group by implentation

In this assignment, I use JAVA to write a program, Average.java.

This program create a 2D array to stroe employees' data which include employee's ID, current salary, min salary and max salary. Then, I group them into differet groups. Finally, I calculate one of these groups, current salary and get the total of employees' current salaries, the average of employees' current salaries.   